

Contact

- +91 9837394813
- Shivamdubeyagra@gmail.com
- 🕋 Agra, Uttar Pradesh
- Portfolio
- shivamdubeyagra
- in shivam-dubey-agra

Education

Full Stack Web Development

Masai School, Bengaluru Apr 2023 - Dec 2023

Bachelor Of Science (B.sc)

Sri P.P.S College, Etah Sept 2016 - Oct 2020

Technical Skills

JavaScript

React

MongoDB

Node.js

Express.js

Soft Skills

Teamwork

Problem Solving

Certifications

Python Programming Infomatics Certification Link 69

C Programming Infomatics Certification Link 69

Shivam Dubey

Full Stack Web Developer

Professional Summary

Full stack developer with 1200+ hours of coding practice at Masai School. I've worked on solo and team projects, using my tech skills and teamwork to solve problems. I'm ready and excited to contribute to cool web development projects.

Projects

Journey Makers Live Demo Link Github Repo Link

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

- Created a user-friendly travel platform with login/signup in 5 days using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Implemented user authentication and enabled travel booking.
- Prioritized simplicity and utilized local storage for a seamless platform experience.

Every Sunday

<u>Live Demo Link</u> <u>Github Repo Link</u>

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

- Contributed to Every Sunday travel site: feedback, navbar, exception handling, and validations.
- Implemented secure user/admin authentication and managed booking operations with the cart.
- Worked as a part of a 5-member team on a 5-day project.

Experience

Madhusudan Motors Pvt. Ltd. | Edp Sales

July 2018 - Apr 2019

 Optimized car sales with streamlined processes for increased customer satisfaction.

Rajeev Jan Seva Kendra | Assistant Manager

Aug 2021 - Nov 2022

 Efficiently managed daily operations, providing excellent service and precise computer tasks.